Not cool, dude.
You went from ghosting us
to being frankly a little clingy.
Ah, come on. That tickles.
Come on, Banana.
We gotta find Panthar.
How? It’s not like he’s just gonna fall
out of the sky.
[Panthar] What’s up, guys--
I stand corrected.
I could really use that help.
Come on, we gotta help him.
Against the shroud-infested flying Batman?
Excuse me?
Man who’s a bat?
That’s better.
Time's a wastin'!
Come on! We’re gonna need reinforcements.
Looks like we’re going up.
[growls]
That doesn’t sound like you, man.
That’s not the Echo Wing I know.
[growling]
Well, maybe I would know you
if you hadn’t taken off on us.
Now put me down!
Admittedly, bad choice of words.
Hey!
Is this the only way back up?
How many stairs are there
in this place?
The elevator got destroyed, remember?
My thighs remember.
Stop smashing me into the floor door!
Huh? Where am I?
Panthar, get away!
This is part of their plan!
Plan? What plan?
You gotta get away from me.
I’ve been possessed by the Shroud.
And they want a-- [growls]
Uh-oh…
Here we go again.
Dangit, there's the ice machine.
I can never find the bucket.
Hello and welcome back
to the Swarm Maker 6000.
Reinforcement time!
Let’s make ourselves an army.
Come, my brothers.
We’re going to save Panthar.
[growls] Hurhhh!
[grunts]
Heavy metal time!
[growls]
Let’s see how it feels to get bussed out.
Banana would have loved that.
You got left out in the cold.
Ah, I got greedy.
Alright, let’s get this gooey stuff
out of you.
Get away from me!
This is what they want.
Just because you gave up
on our friendship
doesn’t mean I’m willing
to give up on…
Ours. Damn it.
No, wait! Agh--
[blabbering]
Oh, man. Looks like
the bad guy break’s over.
Eughhh!
Hey, second tier bad guy.
We’re going to save Panthar, you in?
No way. I’m your greatest foe.
Oh, I’m just kidding.
Hold up, guys.
Hey Spike and/or Sprout,
we’re going to save Panthar.
I’m in.
Hey, come on, we’re--
Nevermind.
‘Sup.
Hey, Popcorn guy. We’re hungry.
Hey!
Beastbot, we need your help.
Panthar’s in trouble.
Haha, I know.
I’ve been watching on the screen.
And you didn’t come
and help?
I didn’t hear a "Please."
I hate you so much…
Come on, we got a lot of stairs
to cover.
Stairs? Let’s just take
the freight elevator.
I hate you so much…
I’ve had just about enough
of the door smashing.
But I’m not giving up on you.
[Shroud-infested noises]
True, but you forgot one thing.
My gross, disgusting swamp friend,
who doesn’t leave, by the way,
gave me the power of healing.
Panthar, no!
This was their plan.
They have control of you now.
No way.
Nothing’s got control of me.
I mean, there’s a couple of K-pop songs,
I guess--
Oh, come on!
Ahh!
Alright, everybody.
This is where it landed.
God, Echo Wing,
you scared the crap out of me.
Wait, are you still a bad guy?
Something terrible’s happened.
I’m… I’m sorry.
Oh, thank goodness.
It’s Panthar.
Hey, Panthar!
Hey, guys…
[growling] Hey, guys…
[snarls] Hang on…
Oh, way to go, Echo Wing.
Now you got Panthar swearing.
[growling]
Holy cliffhanger, Batman.
-Man who’s a bat.
-Sorry.